# 今天让我们来康康宝藏男孩郑秀生的日常
Today, let’s see Treasure Boy Zhe Xiu Sheng’s (Da ye) daily life
# 他喜欢唱歌
He likes singing
# 随时来两首小曲
He sings as he please
# 他用实力卖萌
He acts cute
# 实力模仿魏刚强
Imitate Wei Gang Qiang (Er Bai’s apprentice)
# 大爷
Da Ye
# 走了
Leaving
# 他博学多才
He is of great learning and great ability
# 你得有一个正能量
You must hold a positive attitude
# 要给这些孩子们
Tell theories
# 讲出些门门道道来
To the descendant
# 家有大厨 就是幸福
Happy life with a chef at home
# 这样的大爷你爱了吗
Do you like Da Ye like this?
# 今天我们来盘点一下颜值担当孙立新
Let’s now talk about handsom Sun Li Xin (Er Bai)
# 他沉迷诗歌
He loves poetry
# 爹娘深深的系着我的爱恋
# 期待着如期般的守望
# 他金句频频
He tells verse
# 演绎着人间的温暖
Interpreting the warmth of the world
# 靠我们厨师去温暖这个世界
Let us, chefs to warm the world
# 他多才多艺
He is versatil
# 我还学过织毛衣呢
I’ve learned knitting
# 你以为呢
What do you think?
# 无情铁手剥花生
Peeling peanuts
# 最后我们康康别人眼中的他
Finally, let’s see other people’s perspectives of him
# 孙老师啊是我们烹饪界的美男子
Sun is the handsome man in culinary industry
# 烹饪界的中医大夫
The Chinese doctor in culinary industry
# 烹饪界的理论家和哲学家
The theorist and philosopher in culinary industry
# 这样的二伯您喜欢吗
Do you like Er Bai like this?